https://www.californiachampagnes.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - California Sparkling Wines & Champagne Directory
What
isWhat is Champagne?What is the Champagne region of France?What is Rosé?What does brut mean?What is Blanc de Blanc?What is Blanc de Noirs?What is Méthode Champenoise?What is Terroir?What Is A Good Sparkling Wine Glass?What Types Of GrapesWhat is Chardonnay?What is Pinot Noir?What is Pinot Meunier?How toChooseStoreChillOpenPourSaveWineriesNorthern CaliforniaSonoma and MarinNapa ValleyMendocino and LakeSouth BayLivermore ValleyOtherCentral CaliforniaSouthern CaliforniaMoreAboutSparkling Wine Related LinksContactPrivacy PolicyMapsSonoma & Marin CountiesNapa ValleyMendocino & Lake CountiesThe South BayLivermore ValleyOther Northern CaliforniaSouthern CaliforniaCentral California Coast
Select Page
Californiachampagnes.com Privacy PolicyAs a visitor to Californiachampagnes.com, you are in complete control of your privacy. This includes controlling the use of information you provide to Californiachampagnes.com. Californiachampagnes.com is committed to respecting the privacy rights of visitors to the Californiachampagnes.com web site. While visiting our website, we may ask you to provide information that personally identifies you for purposes of interacting with the site.If you give us permission to email you, you will occasionally receive updates from us about special offers, new Californiachampagnes.com video tutorials and services and other noteworthy news. We hope you will find these updates interesting and informative. If you would rather not receive them, please use the unsubscribe link on the bottom of the email sent to you or contact us through this website.This Privacy Policy has been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, and that underlying business models are still not established. Accordingly, this Privacy Policy is subject to change. Any such changes will be posted on this page.Information CollectedCaliforniachampagnes.com automatically collects and tracks various information, including but not limited to, (1) the home server domain names, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, and type of web browser of visitors to Californiachampagnes.com web site.; (2) the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with Californiachampagnes.com via e-mail; (3) Personal Information specifically provided by you in online forms, registration forms, surveys, and contests entries; and (4) user-specific information on what pages visitors access.Third-Party Ad Serving & Audience/Traffic Measurement ServicesOur site uses Google AdSense and Amazon Ads as third party advertising partners, to serve advertisements on the site. Advertising providers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to the Site and other web sites you have visited, allowing targeted advertisements to be delivered to you for products and services in which you might be interested. The Site also uses a third party traffic measurement service (Google Analytics) to analyze how visitors use the Site. Third party advertising providers, advertisers (whose ads are displayed via the advertising provider) and the traffic measurement services used on the Site may use cookies or other similar mechanisms to automatically collect web site usage information.CookiesThere is a technology called “cookies” which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a web site. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to Your browser, which may then be stored on Your computer system. This element of data is a piece of text, not a program, and as such can not contain viruses or harmful programming code. The Site can only access the information from a cookie sent by the site. We cannot access other cookies sent by other web sites or the information contained therein. Californiachampagnes.com does place cookies on visitors’ computer systems. Californiachampagnes.com uses cookies to track usage of the site and further customize Your experience when you are visiting the site. By tracking usage, we can best determine what features of the site best serve you. When you revisit the site, Californiachampagnes.com will recognize you by the cookie and may tailor your visit accordingly. You may decline the cookie by using the appropriate feature of your web client software, if available, however, some functionality of the site may not function properly if you decline the cookie.Opting Out Of Cookies You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s  Ads Settings.  You can further opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the  Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.Californiachampagnes.com Right to Contact UserCaliforniachampagnes.com reserves the right to contact site visitors regarding account status and changes to the Terms of Use agreement, this privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to site visitors.UpdatesThis Privacy Policy is effective as of June 1, 2010. Californiachampagnes.com reserves the right to change or update this Policy, or any other Californiachampagnes.com policy or practice, at any time with reasonable notice to users of the site. Any changes or updates will be effective upon posting to the site. Your continued use of the site following our posting of a change notice will constitute binding acceptance of those changes.
Copyright 2020, California Champagnes
